Guide to the Douglass Cecil North Papers, 1942-2012 and undated RL.00955
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Professional Correspondence, 1950-2012; 1
  - 1996, Dec. - 1997, Jan. (Box 16)
    Brian Levy.
  - 1996, Dec. - 1997, Oct. (Box 16)
    Cambridge University Press and Clark Gibson ms.
  - 1996, Dec. - 1997, Mar. (Box 16)
    National Research Council / Task Force.
  - 1996 - 1997 (1 of 11) (Box 16)
    Contracts.
  - 1996 - 1997 (2 of 11) (Box 16)
    Mario Drago.
  - 1996 - 1997 (3 of 11) (Box 17)
    Federal Papers.
  - 1996 - 1997 (4 of 11) (Box 17)
    Invitations Accepted.
  - 1996 - 1997 (5 of 11) (Box 17)
    Invitations Declined.
  - 1996 - 1997 (6 of 11) (Box 17)
  - 1996 - 1997 (7 of 11) (Box 17)
    Publication Agreements.
  - 1996 - 1997 (8 of 11) (Box 17)
    Paper Review Requests.
  - 1996 - 1997 (9 of 11) (Box 17)
    Recommendations.
  - 1996 - 1997 (10 of 11) (Box 17)
    Travel correspondence.
  - 1996 - 1997 (11 of 11) (Box 17)
    Geoff Hodgson.
  - 1996 - 1997, Board Memberships. (Box 17)
    Kofi A. Annan, Vernon L. Smith and others.
  - 1996 - 1997, Deirdre McCloskey. (Box 17)
    News and letters.
  - 1997, Jan. (Box 17)
    Economist's Statement on Climate Change, Giovanni Dosi and others.
  - 1997, Feb. (Box 17)
    Themis Minoglu, Fred Sherman and others.
  - 1997, Mar. (Box 18)
    Avner Greif, Rudolf Richter and others.
  - 1997, Apr. (Box 18)
    Jacob Neuser, Peter Conn and others.
  - 1997, May (Box 18)
    Giovanni Forconi, Robert W. Fogel and others.
  - 1997, June (Box 18)
    Louis Putterman, Dr. D. Rulof and others.
  - 1997, Jun. - 1997, Aug. (Box 18)
    Pi Sigma Alpha Meeting.
  - 1997, July (Box 18)
    Miguel Urruita Montoya, Wolfgang S. Heinz and others.
  - 1997, July - 1998, June, Invitations, 2 folders (Box 18)
    Allen Buchanan, Jonathan Michie, Michael DeBow, Pablo Abitol, and others.
  - 1997, July - 1998, June, Recommendations and Evaluations, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - 1997, July - 1998, June, Contracts (Box 19)
    Jim Alt, Barry R. Weingast and others.
  - 1997, July - 1998, June, General (Box 19)
    Frank Walsh, Martin Weitzman and others.
  - 1997, July - 1998, June, Books and Papers, 2 folders (Box 19)
    Robert Singer, Paul Perrier, Roland Vaubel, Janne Hukkinen and others.
  - 1997, Aug. (Box 19)
  - 1997, Sept. (Box 19)
    Andy Sloan, Martin Hartl and others.
  - 1997 Oct. (Box 93)
    D. N.'s Activity report
  - 1997, Nov. (Box 19)
    Jean-Philippe Platteau.
  - 1997, Dec. (Box 19)
    International Center for Economic Growth.
  - 1997 - 1998, 3 folders (Box 19)
    Avner Greif, Randy Calvert, Richard Pipes, Avner Greif, Young Back Choi and others.
  - 1998, Mar. 16 (Box 19)
    Austrian economics.
  - 1998, Dec., 2 folders (Box 19)
    Michael Brie, Kurt Annen.
  - 1998, Jan. - 1999, Feb., Papers (Box 19)
    Hayek paper, Whos is Who in Economics and others.
  - 1998 (Box 19)
    Personal summer correspondence.
  - 1998 - 1999 (Box 19)
    Milken Institute.
  - 1998 - 1999, Recommendations and References, 3 folders (Box 19)
  - 1998 - 1999, Invitations, 3 folders (Box 20)
  - 1998 - 1999, Board Memberships (Box 20)
    Israel M. Kirzner, Barry Weigast and others.
  - 1999, Apr. (Box 20)
    Elizabeth Dickhouse.
  - 1999 Apr.-Nov. (Box 93)
    Masahiko Aoki
  - 1999, May (Box 20)
    Price V. Fishback.
  - 1999 May-Jun. (Box 93)
    William Cheng-Wang Huang, Chairman, Hotung Investment Holdings (Taiwan)
  - 1999 Sep. (Box 93)
    Senator Kit Bond
  - 1999 (Box 20)
    Richard W. Davis and Deborah Ventura.
  - 1999-2000, Books and Papers (Box 20)
    The Journal of Economic Education,European Journal of the History of Economic Thought and others.
  - 1999 - 2000, Comments (Box 20)
    Cynthea Read, Chris Mantzavinos and others.
  - 1999-2000 (Box 93)
    Hoover Activity Reports.
  - 2000, Jan. (Box 20)
    Social Science History Institute Board Meeting.
  - 2000 Jan. (Box 93)
    University of Missouri, St. Louis
  - 2000, Jan. - Mar. (Box 20)
    Herb Simon, Stanley Stark and others.
  - 2000 Feb. (Box 93)
    The Idea Channel
  - 2000 Mar. (Box 93)
    The White House
  - 2000 Apr. (Box 93)
    Bertin Martens
  - 2000, Apr. - June (Box 20)
    John Raisian, Heath Pearson and others.
  - 2000, Apr. 24 (Box 20)
    Claudia N. Lopez, Oscar Edmund Diaz and others.
  - 2000, May (Box 20)
    Yang Yao visit.
  - 2000 May (Box 93)
    Public Choice Society
  - 2000 Jun. (Box 93)
  - 2000 Jul. (Box 93)
    Bjorn Lomborg, Chrysostomos Mantzavinos
  - 2000 Aug. (Box 93)
    Michael D. Intriligator
  - 2000 Sep.-Oct. (Box 93)
    McKinsey and Company report
  - 2000, July - Aug. (Box 20)
    F. H. Buckley, John McCaffrey and others.
  - 2000, Sept. - Oct. (Box 20)
    Syed Shariq, Ian Wills and others.
  - 2000, Sept. - 2011, Jul. (Box 20)
    Books and memberships.
  - 2000 Nov.-Dec. (Box 93)
    Edward Elgar Publ.
  - 2000, Nov. - Dec. (Box 20)
    John Taylor, John Drobak and others.
  - 2000 (Box 20)
    BBC documentary.
  - 2000, Recommendations (Box 21)
    Lee Beach, Tapan Mitra and others.
  - 2001, Visiting Scholar, Hoover Institution. (Box 21)
    Pedro N. Taborga.
  - 2001, Subscriptions (Box 21)
  - 2001, Jan. (Box 21)
  - 2001, Apr. (Box 21)
    Giovanni Dosi, Thrainn Eggertsson and others.
  - 2001 Apr.-Sep. (Box 93)
    Vernon Ruttan, Allan French, Richard Swedberg, John Groenewegen
  - 2001, May (Box 21)
    William Kingston, Giovanni Dosi and others.
  - 2001, May, Recommendations (Box 21)
    Kathy E. Manning.
  - 2001, May, Society for Comparative Research (Box 21)
    Ivan Szelenyi.
  - 2001, June (Box 21)
    University of Zagreb.
  - 2001, July (Box 21)
    Paul S. Edwards, Maurice Thurston and others.
  - 2001, Aug. (Box 21)
    James W. Davis, Una Rey and others.
  - 2001, Sept., Economists Allied for Arms Reduction (Box 21)
    Joseph Biden, Kenneth Arrow and others.
  - 2001, Sept. (Box 21)
    Oliver Williamson, Margaret Levi and others.
  - 2001, Oct. (Box 21)
    Jean-Philippe Plateau, Chris Mantzavinos and others.
  - 2001 Oct.-Dec. (Box 93)
    Correspondence includes U. S. Business School in Prague
  - 2001, Nov. (Box 21)
    Wall Street Journal article on market rules.
  - 2000-2001 (Box 93)
  - 2002, 2 folders (Box 21)
    Workshop on Institutional Analysis. Mie Augier, James G. March, Mark Blaug and others.
  - 2002 Jan.-Jun. (Box 93)
    Jim Gwartney, IMF Survey, Mercatus Center, Syed Shariq, Barry Weingast, Ruttan, John Blundell, Vernon Smith
  - 2002 Jul.-Dec. (Box 93)
    Robert McMeekin, Price Fishback, Barry Weingast
  - 2003 (Box 21)
    Merlin Donald, Karen Rensing and others.
  - 2003 Jan.-Jul. (Box 93)
    Candace & Vernon Smith, Fred Witthans, Dan Klein, Geoffrey Hodgson
  - 2003 Aug.-Dec. (Box 93)
    Worlds of Capitalism, Dan Klein, Art Denzau, Warren J. Samuels
  - 2003 (Box 94)
    Princeton University Press
  - 2004, Jan. (Box 21)
    National Commerce and Management Education, Research and Development.
  - 2004 Jan.-Apr. (Box 94)
    Copenhagen Consensus, Victor Nee, Svetozar Pejovich, John H. Munro, Elinor Ostrom
  - 2004, Mar. (Box 21)
    Gerry Everding and others.
  - 2004, Apr. (Box 21)
    Juan Gonzalez Garcia, Julia M. Chismar and others.
  - 2004, May (Box 21)
    Journal of Institutional Economics.
  - 2004 May-Dec. (Box 94)
    Elinor Ostrom, WSJ, Dan Klein, Joseph Stiglitz, Judge Ginsburg
  - 2004, July (Box 21)
    Jerry Hume and Michael W. Grebe about the Bradley Prize.
  - 2004, Aug. (Box 21)
    Paul Wells, Michael Szenberg and others.
  - 2004, Sept. (Box 21)
    Nicolai J. Foss, Jeffrey Friedman and Rene Lindstaedt.
  - 2004, Oct. (Box 21)
    John Wallis and The Future of the Social Sciencess conference.
  - 2004 (Box 94)
    Colorado College visit
  - 2005, Jan. (Box 21)
    Justus Haucap, Scott Wilson and others.
  - 2005 Jan.-Jul. (Box 94)
    Eric Brousseau, Geoffrey Hodgson, Bradley Foundation, Francis Fukuyama, Price Fishback, Vernon Smith
  - 2005, Feb. (Box 21)
    Diane Masters, Laura Davidoff and others.
  - 2005, Mar. (Box 21)
    New Institutional Economics guidebook and Olin International Business Outlook Conference.
  - 2005, Apr. (Box 21)
    Avi Glandon, Evgeny Popov and others.
  - 2005, May (Box 21)
    Mary M. Shirley, John Wallis and others.
  - 2005, June (Box 21)
    Mary M. Shirley, Vernon R. Ruttan and others.
  - 2005, July (Box 21)
    Milagros Piro Mitma, John Zye and others.
  - 2005, Aug. (Box 21)
    Price Fishback and Diane Masters.
  - 2005 Aug,-Sep. (Box 94)
    Joel Mokyr, Ken Binmore, Art Carden, Elinor Ostrom
  - 2005, Sept. (Box 22)
    Matthew Moffett, Michele Horaney and others.
  - 2005, Oct. (Box 22)
    Elias L. Khalil, Anders F. Olofsgard and others.
  - 2005 Oct. (Box 94)
    Bjorn Lomborg, Andreu Mas-Colell, Elinor Ostrom, Francis Fukuyama, Thomas C. Schelling
  - 2005 Nov. (Box 94)
    Vernon Smith, Pascal Boyer, Timur Kuran
  - 2005 Dec. (Box 94)
    Candace & Vernon Smith, Francis Fukuyama, Bjorn Lomborg
  - 2005 (Box 22)
    Evgeny Popov, Geoffrey Hodgson and others.
  - 2005 (Box 94)
    Hoover Institution
  - 2005 (Box 94)
    Lesson Plan: Is Capitalism Good for the Poor? Foundation for Teaching Economics
  - 2005-2006 (Box 94)
    The British Academy
  - 2005-2006 (Box 94)
    Coase Institute (and NSF proposal)
  - 2005-2006 (Box 94)
    Boards
  - 2006 Jan. (Box 94)
    Emily Chamlee-Wright, Timur Kuran, Chrysostomos Mantzavinos
  - 2006, Feb. (Box 22)
    Valerie Cerra, Leandro Gostisa and others.
  - 2006 Feb. (Box 94)
    Robert Mundell, Richard Sousa, Bjorn Lomborg
  - 2006, Mar. (Box 22)
    Fabiana Rossignolo Londero, Eduardo Vasquez Kunze and others.
  - 2006 Mar. (Box 94)
  - 2006, Apr. (Box 22)
    Sher Sandusky, Elisabeth Case, and Brazilian newspaper.
  - 2006 Apr. (Box 94)
    F. H. Buckley
  - 2006 May (Box 94)
    Chris Mantzavinos, Bjorn Lomborg
  - 2006 Jun. (Box 94)
    Sue Anne Batey Blackman (Princeton)
  - 2006 Jul. (Box 94)
    John Nye
  - 2006 Aug. (Box 94)
    Jeffrey Friedman
  - 2006 Sep. (Box 94)
    Michael Wohlgemuth
  - 2006, Sept. (Box 22)
    Valerie Cerra and Elodie Maitre d'Hotel.
  - 2006 Oct. (Box 94)
    Bart J. Wilson
  - 2006 Nov. (Box 94)
    Barry Weingast, Jeffrey Friedman
  - 2006 Dec. (Box 94)
    Elinor Ostrom
  - 2006 (Box 94)
    Darfur Situation Reports – Elie Wiesel Foundation
  - 2006 (Box 94)
    Deutsche Bank Prize
  - 2007 Jan. (Box 94)
    Elisabeth Case, Copenhagen Consensus, Barry Weingast
  - 2007 Feb. (Box 94)
    MindSoc, Price Fishback
  - 2007 Mar. (Box 94)
    A Conceptual Framework for Interpreting Recorded Human History, David Theroux, Stefan Voigt
  - 2007 Apr. (Box 94)
    Robert Virgil, Akiko Suzuki
  - 2007 May (Box 94)
    James K. Galbraith
  - 2007 Jun. (Box 94)
    Beijing Trip
  - 2007 Jul. (Box 94)
    James Gallagher
  - 2007 Aug. (Box 94)
    Elinor Ostrom, Johnny Munkhammar
  - 2007 Sep. (Box 94)
    Barry Weingast, Johnny Munkhammar
  - 2007 Oct. (Box 94)
    John Nye, James Mirrlee, Barry Weingast
  - 2007 Nov. (Box 95)
    Emily Chamlee-Wright
  - 2007 Dec. (Box 95)
    Karen Horn, Deirdre McCloskey
  - 2007 (Box 95)
    Interviews
  - 2007 (Box 95)
    The Blessing Basket Project
  - 2007 Jan.-May (Box 95)
    Hoover
  - 2006-2008 (Box 95)
    Boards/Memberships
  - 2007-2008 (Box 95)
    American Academy of Arts and Sciences
  - 2008 Jan. (Box 95)
    Folder 1: Lee Benham, Karen Horn
  - 2008 Jan. (Box 95)
    Folder 2: Elinor Ostrom, Copenhagen Consensus, Masahiko Aoki
  - 2008 Feb. (Box 95)
    Folder 1: Niclas Berggren, Brian Levy
  - 2008 Feb. (Box 95)
    Folder 2: Niclas Berggren
  - 2008 Mar. (Box 95)
    Folder 1: Mary Morgan, John Wallis, Adam Levine (Cambridge University Press)
  - 2008 Mar. (Box 95)
    Folder 2: Elie Wiesel
  - 2008 Apr. (Box 95)
    Folder 1: Syed Shariq, Barry Weingast, John Wallis, Cambridge University Press
  - 2008 Apr. (Box 95)
    Folder 2: Frederic Sautet, Claire Morgan, Mary Morgan
  - 2008 May (Box 95)
    Folder 1: Barry Weingast, Cambridge University Press, Emily Chamlee-Wright, John Nye
  - 2008 May (Box 95)
    Folder 2: Cambridge University Press
  - 2008 Jun. (Box 95)
    Folder 1: Erhard Friedberg
  - 2008 Jun. (Box 95)
    Folder 2: Barry R. Weingast, John J. Wallis, Cambridge University Press, Emily Chamlee-Wright
  - 2008 Jul. (Box 95)
    Folder 1: Frederic Sautet, Emily Chamlee-Wright
  - 2008 Jul. (Box 95)
    Folder 2: Adam Levine (Cambridge University Press),
  - 2008 Sep. (Box 95)
    Henry N. Butler (Searle Center)
  - 2008 Oct. (Box 95)
    Folder 1: David Primo, Dennis C. Mueller
  - 2008 Oct. (Box 95)
    Folder 2: Chrysostomos Mantzavinos
  - 2008 Nov. (Box 95)
    Folder 1: Chris Mantzavinos, Dennis C. Mueller
  - 2008 Nov. (Box 95)
    Folder 2: Joel Mokyr, Peter Lipsey
  - 2008 Dec. (Box 95)
    Folder 1: John J. Wallis, Barry R. Weingast, Adam Levine
  - 2008 Dec. (Box 95)
  - 2008 Dec. (Box 95)
    Folder 3: Dennis Snower, John J. Wallis, Art Carden, Donald C. Meyer
  - 2008-2009 (Box 95)
    American Academy of Sciences
  - 2008 Nov. (Box 95)
    George Mason University – Chat with David Primo
  - 2008 Dec. (Box 95)
    China visit
  - 2009 Jan. (Box 95)
    Folder 1: John J. Wallis, Marlous van Vaijenburg
  - 2009 Jan. (Box 95)
    Folder 2: Eric Brousseau
  - 2009 Feb. (Box 96)
    Folder 1: Zsuzsa Horvath, Bjorn Lomborg, Syed Shariq
  - 2009 Feb. (Box 96)
    Folder 2: Alexandra Benham, Pauli Steinback
  - 2009 Mar. (Box 96)
    Gregory Clark, Lawrence Harrison, John J. Wallis, Joel Mokyr
  - 2009 Apr. (Box 96)
    Folder 1: Peter Boettke, Barry R. Weingast, Adam Levine
  - 2009 Apr. (Box 96)
    Folder 2: Geoffrey Hodgson
  - 2009 May (Box 96)
    Eric Brousseau, Geoffrey Hodgson
  - 2009 Jun. (Box 96)
    Adam Levine, Lawrence Harrison (Moscow conference), Eric Brousseau
  - 2009 Jul. (Box 96)
    Mercatus Center
  - 2009 Aug. (Box 96)
    Bruce Caldwell, John J. Wallis, Arthur Denzau
  - 2009 Sep. (Box 96)
    Geoffrey Hodgson, Richard Epstein, Yoram Barzel, Bruce Caldwell, John J. Wallis, Barry R. Weingast
  - 2009 Oct. (Box 96)
    Folder 1: Barry R. Weingast
  - 2009 Oct. (Box 96)
    Folder 2: Geoffrey Hodgson, Art Carden
  - 2009 Nov. (Box 96)
    Folder 1: Barry R. Weingast, Norman Schofield, Todd Zywicki
  - 2009 Nov. (Box 96)
    Folder 2: Barry R. Weingast, Lawrence Harrison
  - 2009 Dec. (Box 96)
    Folder 1: Elinor Ostrom, Todd Zywicki
  - 2009 Dec. (Box 96)
    Folder 2: Marjorie Holme
  - 2009 (Box 96)
    Case Western Reserve University
  - 2009 (Box 96)
    Marlous van Waijenburg
  - 2009 (Box 96)
    Hoover Institution – stay from January till March. Includes correspondence.
  - 2009 (Box 96)
    Economics Department Advisory Council
  - 2009 (Box 96)
    invitations
  - 2009 (Box 96)
    Benzonia. Stay at D. N.'s summer house. June, July and December. Includes correspondence
  - 2009 (Box 96)
    M. Boldrin
  - 2010 Jan. (Box 96)
    Folder 1: Dieter Stribrny, World Bank, John J. Wallis, Gabriela Calderon Motta
  - 2010 Jan. (Box 96)
    Folder 2: David Colander, Art Carden, Norman Schofield, Zsuzsa Horvath (Bjorn Lomborg)
  - 2010 Jan. (Box 96)
    Folder 3: Norman Schofield, Lawrence Harrison, David Colander, Brian Levy, Barry R. Weingast
  - 2010 Feb. (Box 96)
  - 2010 Mar. (Box 96)
    Folder 1: Lawrence Harrison, Brian Levy, Onno Schnellekens
  - 2010 Mar. (Box 96)
    Folder 2: Chrysostomos Mantzavinos, Bjorn Lomborg, Onno Schnellekens
  - 2010 Apr. (Box 96)
    Folder 1: Claire Morgan, Jeremy Rifkin
  - 2010 Apr. (Box 96)
    Folder 2: Ronald H. Coase, Huntington conference Moscow
  - 2010 May (Box 97)
    Folder 1: Huntington Conference Moscow
  - 2010 May (Box 97)
    Folder 2: Barry R. Weingast, John J. Wallis, Gabriela Calderon Motta, Claire Morgan, Bjorn Lomborg
  - 2010 Jun. (Box 97)
    Folder 1: Art Carden, John J. Wallis, Peter G. Klein, Lawrence Harrison
  - 2010 Jun. (Box 97)
    Folder 2: Barry R. Weingast, John J. Wallis
  - 2010 Jun. (Box 97)
    Folder 3: John J. Wallis, Lawrence Harrison, Onno Schnellekens
  - 2010 Jul. (Box 97)
    John J. Wallis, David Colander, Lukas Kovanda, Adam Levine, IMF
  - 2010 Aug. (Box 97)
    Folder 1: Ewan Harrison, Marjorie Holme, Mehdyan Seyed, John. J. Wallis
  - 2010 Aug. (Box 97)
    Folder 2: Bjorn Lomborg, Daniel D. Sokol
  - 2010 Sep. (Box 97)
    Folder 1: Barry R. Weingast, Norman Schofield
  - 2010 Sep. (Box 97)
    Folder 2: Simon Szreter, Amitai Etzioni,
  - 2010 Sep. (Box 97)
    Folder 3: John J. Wallis
  - 2010 Sep. (Box 97)
    Folder 4: Evelyn Gick, John J. Wallis, Bjorn Lomborg, Gabriela Calderon Motta, Simon Szreter, Ning Wang
  - 2010 Sep. (Box 97)
    Folder 5: Eric Brousseau, A priori (encyclopaedia entries), Costas Azariadis
  - 2010 Sep. (Box 97)
    Folder 6: Eric Brousseau
  - 2010 Oct. (Box 97)
    Folder 1: Evelyn Gick, Mind Soc (journal), Art Carden
  - 2010 Oct. (Box 97)
    Folder 2: Bjorn Lomborg, Norman Schofield, Art Carden, Mind Soc, Evelyn Gick
  - 2010 Nov. (Box 97)
    Folder 1: Brian Levy, John J. Wallis
  - 2010 Nov. (Box 97)
    Folder 2: Gabriela Calderon Motta
  - 2010 Dec. (Box 97)
    Folder 1: Geoffrey Hodgson, Adam Levine
  - 2010 Dec. (Box 97)
    Folder 2: SSRN. Elie Wiesel
  - 2010 (Box 97)
    Invitations / General Log
  - 2010 (Box 97)
  - 2010 (Box 97)
    American Economic Association 2010 Meeting
  - 2010 (Box 97)
    Onno Schnellekens, Managing Director, PharmAccess Foundation, Amsterdam, The Netherlands
  - 2010 (Box 97)
    Gail Fosler
  - 2011 Jan. (Box 97)
    John J. Wallis, Elinor Ostrom, Monika Streissler (German translation of Violence and Social Orders)
  - 2011 Feb. (Box 97)
    Folder 1: Michael Intriligator, Roger Myerson, Robert Gordon, Zsuzsa Horvath, Thomas Apolte
  - 2011 Feb. (Box 97)
    Folder 2: John J. Wallis, Barry R. Weingast, Monika Streissler, Jerry Hume
  - 2011 Feb. (Box 97)
    Folder 3: Richard Parker, Salamanca (wikipedia entry)
  - 2011 Mar. (Box 97)
    Folder 1: Michael Haupert, Daniel Klein, Barry R. Weingast
  - 2011 Mar. (Box 97)
    Folder 2: Jorge Jose
  - 2011 Mar. (Box 97)
    Folder 3: Brian Levy, Eric Brousseau, Gail Fosler, Bjorn Lomborg, Mind Soc, Evelyn Gick, Norman Schofield, Nake Kamrany, Barry R. Weingast, John J. Wallis, Adam Levine
  - 2011 Mar. (Box 97)
    Folder 4: Barry R. Weingast
  - 2011 Apr. 9 (Box 98)
    Garden Party for Douglass North
  - 2011 Apr. (Box 98)
    Folder 1: Kyle Bruce, Michele Boldrin, Edward Elgar (Publisher)
  - 2011 Apr. (Box 98)
    Folder 2: Victor Nee, Norman Schofield, Bjorn Lomborg, Art Carden, Michael Munger
  - 2011 May (Box 98)
  - 2011 May (Box 98)
    Folder 2: Gail Fosler, Douglas Webster
  - 2011 May (Box 98)
    Folder 3: Douglas Webster, Michael Haupert
  - 2011 Jun. (Box 98)
    Folder 1: Bruce Caldwell, Rob Shannon
  - 2011 Jun. (Box 98)
    Folder 2: Douglas Webster, David Theroux, Ivan Dimov, Bruce Caldwell, Ronald H. Coase
  - 2011 Jul. (Box 98)
    Folder 1: Joel Mokyr, Norman Schofield, David Theroux, Cambridge University Press, Barry R. Weingast, John J. Wallis, Bruce Caldwell
  - 2011 Jul. (Box 98)
    Folder 2: Michael J. Haupert, John S. Meyer, Gail Fosler
  - 2011 Aug. (Box 98)
    Folder 1: Lee James Alston, Ewan Harrison, Daniel D. Sokol, Barry R. Weingast, Jerry Evensky, Victor Nee
  - 2011 Aug. (Box 98)
    Folder 2: Peter Boettke, Leslie Marsh, Barry R. Weingast, Gail Fosler, John J. Wallis
  - 2011 Sep. (Box 98)
    Folder 1: Price Fishback, Evelyn Gick, Simon Szreter, Ning Wang, Gabriela Calderon Motta, Michael Intriligator
  - 2011 Sep. (Box 98)
    Folder 2: Costas Azariadis, John J. Wallis, Gail Fosler
  - 2011 Sep. (Box 98)
    Folder 3: Leslie Marsh, Gabriela Calderon Motta
  - 2011 Oct. (Box 98)
    Folder 1: Lawrence Harrison, John J. Wallis, Norman Schofield, Art Carden
  - 2011 Oct. (Box 98)
  - 2011 Nov. (Box 98)
    Zsuzsa Horvath (Bjorn Lomborg), Art Carden
  - 2011 Dec. (Box 98)
    John J. Wallis, Pascal Boyer, Syed Shariq
  - 2012 Feb. (Box 98)
    Thomas König, Dale Mott
  - 2012 Mar. (Box 98)
    Barry. R. Weingast
  - 2012 Apr. (Box 98)
    Zsuzsa Horvath (Bjorn Lomborg),
  - 2012 May (Box 98)
    Geoffrey Hodgson, Zsuzsa Horvath (Bjorn Lomborg)
  - 2012 Jun. (Box 98)
    Alexander Field, Robert Leeson
  - 2012 Jul. (Box 98)
    Pascal Boyer
  - 2012 Aug. (Box 98)
    Alex O'Connell (Edward Elgar)
- Conferences and Seminars, 1963-2012; 2
  Files document North's active participation in conferences and lectures chiefly from the 1960s to 2012. Many of the conference programs concern economic history, economic growth, and institutional change. In addition to correspondence and schedules related to conference and travel planning, files often contain drafts of lectures given by North or notes he took during conference proceedings. Arranged chronologically.
  - 1963 Sept., Conference on Research in Income and Wealth, UNC-CH (Box 23)
  - 1968 - 1971, Economic History Association Meeting, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - 1969, Columbia University Seminar in Economic History (Box 23)
  - 1975 Dec. 28, "The Blind Man and the Elephant" AHA Meetings, Atlanta (Box 23)
  - 1975, Exports and Growth Conference (Box 23)
  - 1978 Aug. 13-19, "Seventh International Economic History Congress," Edinburgh (Box 23)
  - 1979 May. 4 - 5, Association of Ancient Historians, Seattle (Box 23)
  - 1979 Sept. 20, Houston Philosophical Society: "The Shortcomings of Economics" (Box 23)
  - 1979 Oct. 4, Austrian Economic Association (Box 23)
  - 1980 Jan. 4, AAAS Meeting Symposium: "New Approaches to Explaining Cultural Complexity" (Box 23)
  - 1980 July 7-17, Liberty Fund Series Conference on "Rationality, Ideology, and Individuality" (Box 23)
  - 1980 Sept. 21-24, Liberty Fund: "The Political Economy of the Transfer Society" (Box 23)
  - 1981 Apr. 19, Talk at George Mason University (Box 23)
  - 1981 Apr. 30-May 2, Cliometrics Conference (Box 23)
  - 1981 June 25-27, Conference at Memorial University of Newfoundland (Box 23)
  - 1981 Visit to Herman Wold - University of Sweden/University of Geneva (Box 23)
  - 1983 Feb. 1, "The Growth of Government" (Box 24)
  - 1983 June 7-10, Seminar on New Institutional Economics (Box 24)
  - 1983 Sept. 3, APSA Meeting, Chicago (Box 24)
  - 1983 Sept. 23-25, Economic History Association annual meeting (Box 24)
  - 1983 Sept., "Government and the Costs of Exchange in History": EHA Meeting (Box 24)
  - 1983 Oct. 25-27, Conference on Federal Regulation, Free Trade, Protection (Box 24)
  - 1983 Nov. 1, Conference: "Spatial and Temporal Trends and Cycles in Chinese Economic History" (Box 24)
  - 1983 Nov. 4, Talk in Chicago (Box 24)
  - 1983 Nov. 10-11, University of Illinois lectures (Box 24)
  - 1983 Nov. 11, Economic History and Comparative Systems Workshop (Box 24)
  - 1984 Jan. 5, Bellagio Conference on Chinese History (Box 24)
  - 1984 Jan. 30, "Political Economy in Historical Perspective" WU Assembly Lecture (Box 24)
  - 1984 Feb. 1, University of Minnesota AG/Econ Seminar (Box 24)
  - 1984 Feb. 14-15, Washington University Alumni Association and Law and Lib. (Box 24)
  - 1984 Feb. 17, University of Indiana talk (Box 24)
  - 1984, Spring Seminar Schedules (Box 24)
  - 1984 Mar. 22-24, "Conference on Research in Income and Wealth" (Box 24)
  - 1984 Mar. 29-31, Public Choice Meetings (Box 24)
  - 1984 Apr. 6-8, Emory University: Law and Economics of Immigration Policy (Box 24)
  - 1984 Apr. 26, Panel, Brown University: "Theoretical Perspectives on States and Markets" (Box 25)
  - 1984 Apr. 27-28, Providence Seminar, Lafayette College Seminar (Box 25)
  - 1984 Apr. 30, "Economic Issues in Historical Perspective" lecture (Box 25)
  - 1984 May 2-3, "Politics and Governance in Market Economies" conference (Box 25)
  - 1984 May 9, Knox College Seminar (Box 25)
  - 1984 May 11, Greater Chicago Economic History Dinner (Box 25)
  - 1984 May 13-15, Henry R. Luce Professors Symposium (Box 25)
  - 1984 May 18, Cliometrics Conference, Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 25)
  - 1984 Jun. Conference on Rationality and Collective Action (Box 25)